trafficswarm.com 2019-05-06

# A Swarm of Free Traffic to Your Site Guaranteed! Get Targeted Free Advertising with TrafficSwarm.com

## TrafficSwarm Privacy Policy

TrafficSwarm.com takes your privacy seriously, and has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy.

Please read the following to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information.

**IP Addresses**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our web server, and for the general administration of our website. Your IP address, should you decide to create a TrafficSwarm account, is also used to prevent you from registering twice due to temporary technical problems.

**Cookies**

Upon your first visit to this web site, a "cookie" is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, however, in no way does this tell us who you are. TrafficSwarm.com has two primary uses for its cookies.

First, we use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate our website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers and/or promotions over and over, or after you have indicated you are not interested in a particular offer. We also use cookies to help track referring web sites.

While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

**Information Gathering**

This web site collects online contact information in various ways, including inquiry forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests. The information collected may be used to send the user information about our company, or to get in touch with the user when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out/modify section below.

The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site, during registration and when you participate in surveys or contest may include, without limitation, any of the following: your full name, street address, e-mail address, password, date of birth, ethnicity, and gender. In addition, we may request information about your use of, or interest in, the types of products and services offered by the third party sellers with whom we have partnered to offer you the products and services available at the Site.

  **Will TrafficSwarm.com disclose the information it collects to others?**  
TrafficSwarm.com does not rent, sell or share any of the information collected by this site with unrelated 3rd-parties, except to provide the products or services you've purchased or requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in conjunction with illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TrafficSwarm.com's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;
  * We may share your user information with carefully selected and well-respected service providers or other companies that provide marketing services on our behalf or to other providers with whom we have joint marketing agreements;
  * We are required by law to provide the IRS with Tax ID numbers and/or other personally identifiable information about Affiliates who promote TrafficSwarm.com and earn over $600 in commissions in a calender year;
  * We may share your user information with carefully selected and well-respected service providers or other companies that provide marketing services on our behalf or to other providers with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

None of the information that is collected by this web site is rented, sold, or shared with any 3rd parties in any way, for any purpose.

**Security**

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

**Opt-Out/Modify**

TrafficSwarm.com provides every user with the opportunity to easily opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether. You may do so in the following ways:

1\. Email: customersupport@trafficswarm.com   
2\. Postal Mail: 1875 Lawrence Street, Suite 750, Denver, CO 80202 USA  
3\. FAX: (734) 661-0173  
4\. Phone: (720) 316-2204  
5\. Website: You may also login to your account at any time to change, delete inaccuracies, or modify your personal information.  
6\. You may also unsubscribe from receiving communications from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication.  
7\. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

  If you simply want to cancel your TrafficSwarm.com account, you may also do so at the following URL: <https://www.trafficswarm.com/cancelacct.pl>

 Your account information will be instantly and completely removed and will not be recoverable. **  
Contacting TrafficSwarm.com**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us via one of the methods above. All disputes will be handled promptly and fairly.
